joomlajunkie.com 2013-04-13

# Privacy Policy - Joomlajunkie

#### Introduction

Privacy Policies are mechanisms used to establish the limits and expectations for the users of JoomlaJunkie resources. External users should have the expectation of complete privacy, except in the case of suspected wrongdoing, with respect to Information Resources.

JoomlaJunkie, knows that your information is private and you are concerned how it is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly.

By visiting JoomlaJunkie, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

The information we gather from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your experience when using our services.

#### Public Access Privacy Policy

Web site Privacy Statement on the Use of Information Gathered from the General Public.

The following statement applies only to members of the general public and is intended to address concerns about the types of information gathered from the public, if any, and how that information is used.

#### 1\. Cookies

A “cookie” is a small file containing information that is placed on a user’s computer by a web server. Typically, these files are used to enhance the user’s experience of the site, to help users move between pages in a database, or to customize information for a user.

Cookie data is not used in any way that would disclose personally identifiable information to outside parties unless JoomlaJunkie is legally required to do so in connection with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings.

#### 2\. Logs and Network Monitoring

JoomlaJunkie maintains log files of all access to its site and also monitors network traffic for the purposes of site management. This information is used to help diagnose problems with the server and to carry out other administrative tasks. Log analysis tools are also used to create summary statistics to determine which information is of most interest to users, to identify system problem areas, or to help determine technical requirements.

**Information such as the following is collected in these files:**  

  * Hostname: the hostname and/or IP address of the computer requesting access to the site.
  * User-Agent: the type of browser, its version, and the operating system of the computer requesting access (e.g., Netscape 4 for Windows, IE 4 for Macintosh, etc).
  * Referrer: the web page the user came fromSystem date: the date and time on the server at the time of access.
  * Full request: the exact request the user made.
  * Status: the status code the server returned, e.g., fulfilled request, file not found.
  * Content length: the size, in bytes, of the file sent to the user.
  * Method: the request method used by the browser (e.g., post, get).
  * Universal Resource Identifier (URI): the location of the particular resource requested. (More commonly known as a URL).
  * Query string of the URI: anything after a question mark in a URI. For example, if a keyword search has been requested, the search word will appear in the query string.
  * Protocol: the technical protocol and version used, i.e., http 1.0, ftp, etc.

The above information is not used in any way that would reveal personally identifying information to outside parties unless JoomlaJunkie is legally required to do so in connection with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings.

#### 3\. Email and Form Information

If a member of the general public sends JoomlaJunkie an e-mail message or fills out a [web-based form](http://www.joomlajunkie.com/contact) with a question or comment that contains personally identifying information, that information will only be used to respond to the request and analyze trends. The message may be redirected to another department or person who is better able to answer your question. Such information is not used in any way that would reveal personally identifying information to outside parties unless System Administration is legally required to do so in connection with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings.

#### 4\. Links

This site may contain links to other sites. JoomlaJunkie is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

#### Private / Paid Access Privacy Policy

This includes all public policy definitions.

All information submitted to us will be used as per the terms and condition of this website. You grant us permission to pass your details over to prospective buyers/sellers for the completion of our services agreement.

All the information contained on this website is copyright of JoomlaJunkie and may not be copied, either in part or in whole. As we respect your privacy, we ask in return that you respect ours.
